

933, Skylark Apartments, Plot 35, Sector 6, Dwarka, New Delhi, India — IN 110075

M +91 8860896000

arizsiddiqui@hotmail.com www.arizsiddiqui.xyz

Profile

Experienced developer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer industry. A individual with strong communication and inter-personal skills, having successfully contributed to team success with hard-work, attention-to-detail and leadership qualities. Currently developing skills in Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning, motivated to grow and excel in the Data Science Industry.

Experience

Associate Technical Lead, Microsoft Learn Student Ambassadors SRM – 2019—Present Completed multiple projects under the banner of the Technical Team of the club, including a NLP based browser extension, a CLI for keeping API and OAuth Tokens safe and a webinar on the basics of Python. Currently working towards nurturing and developing talented yet inexperienced developers.

Committee Member, Aaruush - 2019 - Present

Helped organise one of the largest techno-management fests in South India, playing decisive roles in guest invitation and itinerary management. Personally tended to many high-profile guests and successfully managed crisis situations.

Head Boy, Nirmal Bhartia School - 2018-2019

Served as the head of the Student Council of the school, helping implement regulations that improved the school life of the students.

Web Developer, IN-X Union – 2016 – 2017

Served as a web developer for the school IT Club in Secondary School. Helped organise and manage the techfest Infoyage for 2 years.

Education

SRM Institute of Science and Technology, Kattankulathur, Tamil Nadu

B.Tech. Computer Science and Engineering (2019—2023)

Nirmal Bhartia School, Sector 14, Dwarka, New Delhi

Senior Secondary School (2017-2019)

Skills

Python, C, C++, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Swift, SQL, Git, OpenCV, TensorFlow, Numpy, Pandas, Bootstrap, Scikit-learn, Scipy, Keras.